Alright, so at this point we know we're going to use Scale Type to expand
Tamam, burada, resmimizi genişletmek için scaleType'ı
So, now what I want you to do is actually expand the image to fill
Şimdi sizden yapmanızı istediğim, resmi ekranı dolduracak
the entire screen.
şekilde genişletmeniz.
Now a couple of hints on how to do this.
Bunu yapmak için birkaç ipucu.
Hint number one, now there are actually a lot of different values that you can
Birincisi scaleType için bir sürü değer var,
set Scale Type to, but in the lesson we only taught you about two, so
ancak derste biz size yalnızca ikisini gösterdik,
let's stick with thinking about those.
o yüzden onlarla devam edelim.
The values that we know about are center and center crop.
Bildiklerimiz de center ve centerCrop.
Knowing what you know from the lesson,
Bu dersten öğrendiklerinizle,
which one of these do you think we should use?
bunlardan hangisini kullanmalıyız?
Now once you've used scale type properly to make the image expand to the entire
ScaleType'ı ekran boyunca resmi genişleterek,
screen, there's a possibility that your text will disappear.
uygun bir şekilde kullanırsak, metinin kaybolma ihtimali var.
If this happens to you, try changing around the ordering of your views.
Eğer böyle olursa, görüntülerin sıralamasını değiştirmeyi deneyin.